<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Health Center</string>
    <string name="changeExplain">Here you can change your password, your height and your weight. To save the changes, press on the change button.</string>
    <string name="caloriesExplain">"Calories: Calorie is the sum of energy that needed to heat 1 mm of water at 1 celsius. "
        "Our body work on calories. Every activity that we do needed some of calories."
        "Calories is like gas to our body. We get calories from the food we eat. Every Food has some"
        "of calories that if you ate this food you get those calories. But what happen if we don't use all of the calories that"
        "we ate? Our body make this extra calories to fat. So, if someone want to add some weight to his body,"
        "he should ate more calories then he bern. And what happen if we ate less calories then we bern? our"
        "body will use the fat that we have and bern it instead. So, if someone want to lower some weight to his body,"
        "he should ate less calories then he bern. The average man bern 2,000,000 calories at day. Because that"
        "number is very big, we don't use calories, but kilo-calories, that equal to 1000 calories. But"
        "still most of the people say calories, because it more comfortable."</string>
    <string name="proteinExplain">"Protein: Proteins are the material of our muscles. Our body use protein to rebuild our muscles after we train."
        "during training our muscles destroyed, and when our body rebuilt them, they became larger and stronger (and that how our muscles get bigger and stronger from training to training)"
        "Because of that, our body must get enough protein - to build our muscles again! person that train need to get 1.7-2 times his weight proteins at day (at grams). For example, if a man is"
        "weight 80 kg, he need to eat at least 140 grams of proteins at day. Moreover, proteins are very satisfactory, so it better it proteins then carbohydrates for a person that want to lose weight."
        "Because proteins have less calories then carbohydrates - so he will eat less calories for the same mass of food. Proteins have 4 calories per gram".</string>
</resources>